(Wil:)Are you okay?
(Sheldon:)You're asking a lot of questions,
Wil Wheaton.
(Sheldon:)As a matter of idle curiosity...
(Sheldon:)...which of your shrubberies do you feel
would benefit from a thorough vomiting?
(Sheldon:)Never mind, I'll choose.
(Sheldon:)You were so good in Stand by Me.
(Sheldon:)Hello, I'm Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
(Penny:)Welcome to
Sheldon Cooper Presents Fun With Flags.
(Sheldon:)Get ready for a very special episode...
(Sheldon:)...where we explore the flags of the popular
entertainment franchise Star Trek.
(Sheldon:)And to help us,
I'm pleased to introduce a special guest.
(Sheldon:)Surprisingly, it only took gas money and
the promise of free food to get him here.
(Sheldon:)Mr. LeVar Burton.
(LeVar:)Hey, Sheldon. It's a pleasure to be here.
(LeVar:)- Well, we've got some interesting flags...
- Cut.
(Amy:)Yikes, this guy is worse than Wil Wheaton.
(Sheldon:)I don't know what she's talking about,
but I'm obligated to agree with her.
(Sheldon:)- She's my girlfriend.
- Ah. I hear you, brother.
(LeVar:)I still get lunch, right?